DAD: Come on, buddy.
[dad grunts]
[dog barking]
DAD: Ella.
I need you to wake up.
Ella, come on,
I need you to wake up now.
[whispering] Why?
We're gonna go on a trip.
What time is it?
It's early, Stinks.
Is Charlie okay?
Yeah.
He's fine,
he's already in the car.
Come on, get up.
I need you to think about...
some things that
you want to bring with you.
You want to wear these?
[Ella grunts]
No, no, no, come on.
Please,
I really need your help.
Charlie's already in the car.
I know it's early, sweetheart,
but we gotta go.
[Dad sighs]
Dad, where are we going?
Honey...
pretend that there's a fire
in the house
and we have to get out
as quick as we could.
What would you take with you?
A picture of Mom.
Okay.
What else?
- My DS.
- Where is it?
- It's plugged into the wall.
- Yeah.
Get dressed and hurry up.
- You ready?
- I think so.
I'm gonna grab
a few more things.
Can you get Rex
and put him in the car?
- [Rex barking]
- Okay.
- Rex.
- [Rex barking]
Rex, come here.
Come here, boy.
Come here.
Come on.
Here.
Gosh.
Okay.
DAD: Becky, I think it's okay.
We're all ready...
We gotta try...
If we just head East...
Dad?
Hey, Stinks.
ELLA:
There's Sheriff Lady outside.
Oh, okay.
- SHERIFF: Good morning.
- Hi.
Ella, get in the car, please.
Sir?
Sir, can you step over here?
You know what's happening here,
what do you need to talk about?
SHERIFF: ...to the owner
of the property.
I'm asking you
one last time...
as a courtesy.
Is there anything else?
DAD:
I grabbed everything I could.
Can we go?
Thank you.
Put that in the glove box.
You ready?
[engine cranks]
[Dad sighs]
Come on.
[pensive music playing]
Ella, hop in.
[engine stalls]
Let's try again.
[Dad grunts]
[Ella grunts]
- DAD: Are you buckled in yet?
- ELLA: I'm trying to.
CHARLIE: Rex, know what
this is? A wagon.
A boat.
A bus.
A car.
A truck.
Ella, he licked the book again.
ELLA: Ewww.
Wagon, sled, boat,
bus, car, truck,
train, airplane.
I'm hungry.
DAD: Oh, you're hungry?
Nice to meet you, hungry.
All right, we're gonna go in
and each grab a snack
and a drink.
I'm gonna use the restroom.
Make sure
your brother stays with you.
Can I get Sour Patch Kids?
What if we got
glazed strawberry?
They look good.
Let me look at the calories.
160 calories.
ELLA: See, it's 70 calories
less than Sour Patch Kids.
But you know what?
This one's better
because it has more.
You guys get your stuff?
Charlie.
[country music
on radio playing]
- CLERK: This gonna be it?
- DAD: Yep.
Comes out to $6.82.
How far are
the Salt Flats from here?
CLERK: Three hours.
DAD: How much are these?
CLERK: $4.99.
Comes out to $17.47.
I thought you said
they were $4.99.
CLERK: I meant each.
Just take one.
Dad, can I get this?
I got you a kite, buddy.
All right, let's go.
- CHARLIE: Dad, look at these.
- Come on, Charlie.
CHARLIE: Can you just
look at this? Look.
DAD: That's cool, let's go.
Did Dad say where we're going?
Yeah, on a trip.
Wanna read a book, Rex?
Oh, you don't wanna read.
You wanna lick the pavement.
I think
we're going to Disneyland.
I think we're moving.
DAD: What?
- Mm.
- [Charlie laughs]
Oh, they smell so good.
Oh, that one smells
even better.
["I Hear You Calling"
by Kevin Morby playing]
♪ I hear you calling ♪
♪ From the riverbank ♪
CHARLIE: You want one, Dad?
They're really good.
I'm all right, buddy.
I'll take one.
♪ I will be coming ♪
♪ When the air is black ♪
♪ All my time is lying ♪
♪ On the factory floor ♪
[indistinct]
DAD: Do you want ice cream?
- CHARLIE: I always
want ice cream.
- DAD: Yeah?
CHARLIE: I always want
ice cream. I'm a kid.
♪ I hear you calling ♪
["Mony Mony" by Tommy James
and The Shondells playing]
[Charlie laughing]
CHARLIE: It's Mom's favorite.
♪ Here she comes now, say,
Mony, Mony ♪
♪ Well, shoot 'em down,
turn around, come on, Mony ♪
Dad, look.
♪ Hey, she gives me love
and I feel alright now ♪
♪ You got me tossin', turnin'
in the middle of the night ♪
♪ I say, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ She comes now, say,
Come on, Mony ♪
♪ Come on, Mony ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ You make me feel so good ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, good ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ So good ♪
♪ Alright ♪
♪ I say yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
CHARLIE:
Dad, how fast are you driving?
The speed limit.
CHARLIE: Rex, fell with
his face on the...
DAD: We're here.
You got it?
- CHARLIE: Dad, is this where
we're going?
- DAD: What do you mean?
- CHARLIE: Are we staying here?
- DAD: No, we're just getting
some food in our stomachs.
Then, we keep on going.
CHARLIE: Come on,
Ell-a-Smell-a.
[baby groaning]
- DAD: Come on, let's eat.
- CHARLIE: Okay.
- I got yours.
- Racer X.
Dad, can we play after we eat?
DAD: We'll see.
Rex.
Dad, dogs aren't supposed
to eat people food.
Dog food is made out of meat.
This is meat. The only
difference is that this meat
is actually fresh,
and dog food
is the kind of meat that
you guys wouldn't eat,
like the nose and the tail.
Buttholes of the cow.
Put it
in these tiny little pieces.
It's like 20 bucks, Ella.
DAD: This is the same thing.
- But better.
- But better, right.
See? Charlie knows.
- Dad.
- Enough, Ella.
Enough.
CHARLIE: Dad,
could I have a dollar?
I want to split
a sundae with Charlie.
Thanks.
DAD:
You gotta eat it in the car.
Charlie, want any more
of this food, bud?
CHARLIE: Come on, stinky butt.
ELLA: I'm gonna get you.
[both chuckling]
- Oh, I got it, I got it!
- CHARLIE: I got.
[both chuckling]
Okay.
Probably tonight.
Um, I don't know,
in about an hour.
CHARLIE: Come on!
- You farted!
- ELLA: I did not.
You're a good doggy.
Do you-- Yeah, do you--
So, what time are you open?
It's-- it's not good
for your stomach.
You're going to have
some pet food soon.
[pensive music playing]
Ella, no.
Come play with me.
Ella, look at me.
Thank you.
Bye.
[Charlie laughing]
CHARLIE: Come on! Work with me!
ELLA: Dad...
Where are we going?
Nebraska.
[Charlie coughing]
[radio chatter]
[radio stopping]
DAD: Ella, wake up.
Ella, wake up.
Can you take Charlie out there
and fly a kite with him?
ELLA: Okay.
- DAD: Take Rex, too.
- ELLA: Okay.
Make sure
he goes to the bathroom.
ELLA: Are you ready?
Come on.
DAD: Thanks.
ELLA: Charlie, wait!
CHARLIE: How do you know
how to fly kites?
ELLA: Mom taught me
before she got sick.
And here.
You just stick it
right in here.
And then we've got
our kite ready.
- CHARLIE: Can I go first?
- ELLA: Sure.
You hold this.
You've got to untie it
a little bit.
Okay, start running.
Keep running
until you find the wind.
[gentle melody playing]
Lift it up.
CHARLIE: I am, Ella.
Here, let me help you.
Let me help you.
ELLA: Make it look similar
as you run.
CHARLIE:
Okay, I get it, Ella.
ELLA:
Can I teach you a trick?
Ready?
Okay, start running.
[Charlie laughing]
ELLA: You did it!
[both laughing]
Run!
Wow, yeah!
You can let it go
while you're running.
-Let it go!
-I'll let go now.
ELLA: Let go!
Come here, Rex.
ELLA: Here, wanna try, Charlie?
I'll be right back,
just wait here.
Come on, Rex.
- CHARLIE: What are you doing?
- DAD: I'll be right back.
[Rex barking]
[ominous tone playing]
Ella, get in the car.
- Ella!
- No!
- Stop. Stop.
- No, no!
Dad. [sobbing]
Get in the car. We're going.
- We're going.
- Dad, you can feed him
people food.
- DAD: Ella, stop it.
- I don't care.
- You can feed him people food.
- Stop it, Ella,
stop it right now.
- I'm sorry.
- No, Dad, you can feed him
as many hamburgers as you like.
- I don't care!
I shouldn't have said anything!
- It's not that.
ELLA:
I'm sorry I said anything!
- Dad!
- ELLA: Please.
[Ella sobbing]
DAD:
Ella, please, we gotta go.
[Ella crying]
- Stop, stop, stop!
- No!
Stop, stop! Come here.
[whispering] Stop.
Stop. Stop.
CHARLIE: Dad!
Get the dog
and then come back in here
and then we'll go!
[sorrowful music playing]
I'm sorry.
It's for the best.
Dad!
[whispering] I'm sorry.
[Ella sobbing]
No.
ELLA: Here.
Lift your arms up.
CHARLIE: Is Dad mad at us?
ELLA: I don't know.
[water gurgling]
Are we gonna stay here
lots of days?
Just gonna stay tonight
and then we gotta keep moving.
To Nebraska?
Mm-hmm.
CHARLIE: Dad.
I want Rex.
DAD: I want a lot
of things, Charlie.
But it doesn't always
work out the way you plan.
[melancholic music playing]
Wanna see who can hold
their breath the longest?
Yeah?
Are you ready? One, two, three.
CHARLIE:
Winner, winner, chicken dinner.
You did not.
You popped up like five times.
What, what, what?
- Dad!
- Ah, buddy!
Dad!
- [Charlie chuckling]
- DAD: Tell Ella to jump.
DAD: [mumbling]
I had to get Rex.
No, Molly, he's upset.
You know, Molly,
they don't like it.
Charlie too.
I don't know, [indistinct].
Tell me what to do.
[pensive music playing]
[engine cranks]
[engine stalls]
DAD: All right, let's go.
- Okay, you ready?
- ELLA: Yep.
- DAD: One, two, three!
- ELLA: Push.
DAD: All right, get in.
One try.
DAD: Go inside and pay?
- ELLA: Yeah.
- CHARLIE: Okay.
When you go inside,
say that you want $20
on pump number two.
- Okay?
- Okay, cool.
- DAD: What did I say?
- $20 on pump number two.
In fact, you don't even
have to say pump.
- Just say $20 on two.
- ELLA: $20 on two.
- DAD: Here.
- Can I go?
- ELLA: Thanks.
- Say it again, what is it?
- ELLA: $20 on two.
- You got it.
- Can I go?
- No.
- Can I go, Dad?
- DAD: Sure, Charlie.
- ELLA: Dad.
- DAD: Ella.
CHARLIE: I'll put my sandwich
here, okay, Dad?
DAD: All right, perfect.
You better get out or
your sister's gonna leave you.
All right, come on, buddy.
CHARLIE:
I could have opened it myself.
Well, I didn't know
if you were going to.
Make sure
you go to the bathroom.
BOTH: Okay.
Don't take anything.
CHARLIE: I'm not.
Oh, sorry, there's a little
girl in line behind me.
I'm sorry.
Line's moving up,
so I gotta keep going.
Thanks.
Her little fingers
are so adorable.
Aren't they so cute? Say hi.
They're so tiny.
Hello, little girl.
- WOMAN: Where you headed?
- ELLA: Nebraska.
Nebraska? I'm from there.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna see
some family in Utah.
They haven't met
this little one yet.
That's my brother, Charlie.
He's afraid that
Nebraska's gonna be boring.
Ah, yeah,
a lot of people think that,
but I love it.
[child yelling in distance]
If you do make it to Omaha,
make sure you guys
go to the zoo, okay?
It's pretty, not boring,
and I'm sure
your brother will love it.
Thank you.
Okay.
Bye, little one.
Bye.
You're next.
Twenty on two, please.
Thanks.
Charlie?
Charlie!
- Keep that on, bud.
- CHARLIE: Okay.
- DAD: Work out okay?
- ELLA: Yeah.
[engine starts]
DAD: Would you rather be a fish
or a bird?
I choose a bird.
DAD: Okay, fine, if you were
a bird, you can only fly,
you can never land.
Or you can be a fish and
never come out of the water.
Yeah, I could land.
Because I'll only be able
to stay in the water as a fish.
Are we going to Omaha?
What?
In Nebraska,
are we going to Omaha?
What do you mean?
In the gas station,
a lady said that
if we go to Omaha,
we should go to the zoo.
And that it's pretty awesome,
and Charlie would like it.
Can we go?
I don't know.
Dad?
MOM: [on speaker] Do you want
to help me sing, Ella?
ELLA: Yeah.
MOM: Charlie,
do you want to help too?
CHARLIE: I'm the boat.
MOM: Here we go.
♪ In the pines ♪
♪ In the pines,
where the sun never shines ♪
♪ And the shiver
when the cold winds blow ♪
♪ My love, my love,
what have I done ♪
♪ To make you treat me so ♪
♪ You've caused me to weep ♪
♪ You've caused me to mourn ♪
♪ You've caused me
to lose my heart ♪
♪ In the pines, in the pines ♪
♪ Where the sun never shines ♪
♪ And the shiver
when the cold winds blow ♪
♪ The longest train
that ever I saw ♪
What are you doing?
Sticking your head
out the window.
Don't do stupid shit like that.
You need to grow up.
[singing in background]
Ella, you're almost
ten years old.
[singing in background]
I need to know
that you can be responsible.
Can you be responsible?
[singing in background]
Are you okay, Ella?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Dad, you said a bad word.
That means
you have to buy us ice cream.
We'll get ice cream
at the next stop.
[wind whooshing]
CHARLIE: Would you rather
pick up someone's vomit
or let someone pee
in your mouth and swallow it?
ELLA: Gross, Charlie.
- Or.
- Or isn't it a thing, right?
- You have to pick.
- I'm not answering that.
It's nasty.
Would you rather
eat five rotten cheese slices
or lick a dirty toilet?
How dirty is the toilet?
It's like the toilet
at the gas station.
That's the terriblest
toilet ever.
Okay, lick the toilet.
CHARLIE: Ew, you're going
to lick up all that poop.
You're going to have
poop in your mouth.
Not in the girls bathroom.
Then when you talk to Dad,
he'll be like who farted?
- "Who you farted?"
- DAD: Let's finish that up.
Are we close, Dad?
Kind of.
We'll keep driving
through the night, so...
probably won't get there
until really late.
- You'll be asleep.
- No way.
DAD: It'll be, like,
four in the morning, Charlie.
I can stay up that long.
[car engine sputtering]
["Ross Ross Ross" by Sebastian
playing over radio]
Charlie, what are you doing?
ELLA: Stop it.
♪♪♪
CHARLIE: Check out my moves.
Check out my moves!
- [Ella laughs]
- Come dance with me.
Oh, no, I can't.
[Ella giggles]
Hey, go inside
and wash your hands.
[kids giggling]
It doesn't work.
[Ella chuckles] Yeah, it does.
Spoke too soon. Get down.
Put that down.
Now lather it up.
- [Charlie laughs]
- Lather it up.
What does that mean?
It means--
Oh, don't, don't, don't.
Oh, don't get soap everywhere.
It means rub it together
and then all around.
Until you get
soapy cream like mine.
[paper towel
dispenser whirring]
Come on.
Charlie.
[gentle music playing]
[engine rumbling]
CHARLIE: Dad,
would you rather
eat someone's boogers
or lick
a piece of their poop?
DAD: Well, I like to eat poop,
so I guess I'd eat poop.
- CHARLIE: Seriously, Dad?
- DAD: What?
In some countries,
that's a delicacy.
But do you like boogers?
CHARLIE: Wait.
I like to eat my boogers.
They taste salty.
- Boogers?
- Yeah.
- Poop tastes sweet.
- Ew, gross.
- It tastes--
- Did you try it?
It tastes like
a tornado in your mouth.
Mm-hmm.
Have you ever had
a tornado in your mouth?
Yeah, when I had poop.
["Warped Window"
by Anna Mieke playing]
♪ I have been wandering long ♪
Hey, grab me
another pillow.
[Charlie groans] Found one.
- Thanks.
- Thank you, Charlie.
- This one's more soft.
- Thank you.
♪ Oh, so delicate,
delicate frame ♪
CHARLIE: Are you gonna drive
and not get any rest?
I'll sleep eventually,
Charlie, but thanks.
- Sleep when you're driving.
- I'm not gonna do that.
♪ Brittle boned,
you sat crouched and decayed ♪
I'm gonna stop here.
I gotta take a leak.
♪ Two hundred years ♪
What's a leak?
♪ Or more ♪
♪ Wrinkled map on skin,
on floor ♪
- [car horn honking]
- [kids laughing]
♪ Warped window wood ♪
Would you rather...
♪ Time had bent it good ♪
[engine humming]
♪ Warped window wood ♪
♪ Life had bent it
where it stood ♪
♪ Thought of you
in the deep of my sleep ♪
[fireworks popping]
[uplifting music playing]
[overlapping shouting]
[Dad sighs]
Dad, can we go
to the zoo tomorrow?
[groans]
We'll see, sweetheart.
[gentle music playing]
[fireworks popping]
[sobbing]
[fireworks crackling]
♪♪♪
I'm just tired.
[Dad sighs]
[fireworks popping]
[road din]
[radio show playing]
CHARLIE:
Are we in Nebraska?
ELLA: I think so.
- CHARLIE: Dad?
- DAD: Yeah?
CHARLIE: Can you--
can you open this pen?
Mm-hmm.
- Here you go, buddy.
- CHARLIE: Thanks.
[engine rumbling]
Here, Dad.
DAD:
Are those monsters, buddy?
CHARLIE:
It's us on our trip.
The one in the middle
is you.
The one on the right
is me.
The one on the left
is Ella.
DAD: You look like
you have claws.
I do.
Because I'm a dragon.
I'll put it right here.
[engine rumbling]
Let's go, bud.
It's hot.
- Come on.
- Let's eat some lunch.
[kids laughing]
["Tick Tick Boom"
by The Hives playing]
♪ Tva tre ♪
[Charlie screaming]
- Sorry.
- ELLA: Sorry.
You almost hit her.
♪ I was right all along ♪
- [Charlie belches]
- ELLA: Ew.
You guys are gross.
Let's be quick.
You want Lunchables?
This-- hey give me that.
I'm-- I'm giving it to you.
I want pizza.
- Give it to me, Ella.
- Hey, hey.
Faster.
[overlapping chatter]
[kids screaming]
[till beeping]
CASHIER: Hey,
you find everything you needed?
Yeah.
- Charlie, what are you doing?
- [cashier chuckles]
- CHARLIE: Can I get this?
- What, do you want that?
- Sorry.
- CASHIER: It's okay. [laughs]
I'll go ahead
and swap out the...
DAD: Thanks.
So, $25.33 is your total.
Uh, is that going to be EBT
food stamps or cash aid, sir?
- It's food.
- Okay.
Uh, just press this button.
[till beeping]
Uh, it declined.
You only have $20.43 left
on your food stamps.
Okay, can I take
something off?
Yeah, sure.
What would you
like for me to take off?
The pizza Lunchable.
Okay.
$21.35.
And the soda.
You want to do something fun?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
I thought we were
going to do something fun.
- Oh, Dad--
- Dad--
Are we gonna go to the--
Can I just surprise you?
Yeah?
I'll be surprised right now
if you just tell me.
[engine clicking]
[radio show playing]
[engine rumbling]
[sighs]
CHARLIE: Dad, come on.
Where are we going?
This way, Charlie.
Almost there.
- Careful, Charlie.
- Okay.
How far is it, Dad?
It's close.
Isn't that awesome?
Ella, isn't that awesome?
One adult and two kids.
How old are your kids?
Nine and six.
CASHIER: $30.50.
[gentle music playing]
DAD: Hang on to this.
CASHIER: And then
your three tickets.
DAD: Thank you.
- Can I have the panda one?
- DAD: Yeah.
[birds chirping]
[kids laughing]
So adorable.
[kids exclaiming]
[colobus squeaking]
♪♪♪
Look at that one.
It's facing us... [indistinct]
- You see it?
- CHARLIE: Yeah.
[kids laughing]
CHARLIE: Let's go.
♪♪♪
- There's chickens.
- ELLA: Look at that bird.
CHARLIE:
Look at that big ostrich.
Oh, my God.
Gross. My turn.
CHARLIE: How crazy it would be
to have a pet like a bear.
ELLA: Oh,
I'll bring him to school.
CHARLIE: For show and tell.
[kids laughing]
[Ella and Charlie
murmuring indistinctly]
...Or get pecked in the eye
by an ostrich?
I'm higher than you.
CHARLIE:
♪♪♪
You see? Look at that one.
He's moving over there.
[laughs]
He just rolled over.
- [lion roaring]
- [kids laughing]
Stop it.
Stop your fussing.
- Stop your fussing.
- DAD: Guys, do not fight.
- We have to fight.
- No, you don't.
Imagine if I was a giraffe.
How would I even get
this cracker to my mouth?
Oh. Like that.
What's wrong
with these Lunchables?
No, you eat your food.
It's okay.
- Thank you, Elle.
- Okay.
You actually have more than me,
but I just traded.
[Charlie slurping]
- You a fish?
- [Charlie laughs]
Can I hold it?
Do you want to hold this one?
He's really calm.
Look, Ella.
[chuckles] They're playing.
Oh. [chuckles]
They always fly away.
Can I catch the monarch?
There's a big one.
All the way up there.
- Can you see that one?
- DAD: Yeah.
- It's orange.
- DAD: Mm-hmm.
The monarchs are
the big beautiful orange ones.
[gentle music playing]
[Ella chuckles]
Isn't this so cool, Dad?
It's pretty great, Stinks.
You have to put
your finger underneath...
- DAD: Like that?
- ...In the front...
DAD: All right,
let me try that.
...And then you pick it up.
[grunts] Come here, buddy.
- CHARLIE: Be careful.
- I'm trying to be careful.
- In the front.
- DAD: In the front? Like this?
How do you make it fly?
I want to let go.
CHARLIE:
It's coming up to me. [laughs]
ELLA: It's about
to fly on your head.
It's flapping on your head.
It's like, "I'm going
to make a nest in this head.
"I'm going to live there."
[indistinct chatter]
[breathing heavily]
[wings flapping]
[waves crashing]
[engine rumbling]
CHARLIE: I really like
that dad took us out here.
ELLA: Would you rather
a leopard or a bear?
CHARLIE: A leopard.
ELLA: Would you rather
a leopard or a moose?
CHARLIE: A leopard.
ELLA: Would you rather
a leopard or a fox?
CHARLIE: Um, a fox.
ELLA: Would you rather
a fox or a deer?
CHARLIE: A fox.
ELLA: Would you rather
a fox or an ostrich?
Ostrich.
[brakes squealing]
[Dad panting]
What are we doing?
What are we doing, Dad?
Dad, what are we doing?
Let's get out
of the car, guys.
[car beeping]
Come on.
[door shuts closed]
[bell dinging]
[car horn honking]
[somber music playing]
Dad, can we swim again
like we did before?
ELLA: Dad, can we go
back to the hotel room?
[siren wailing]
CHARLIE:
Found some more cracks.
[road din]
ELLA:
Why are we going here?
Dad, what are we doing?
I'm going to go back to the car
and grab something.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Hold on to this.
Okay, don't lose it.
- It's important.
- CHARLIE: Dad,
we should go with you.
Hold on to Charlie,
all right?
Hold Charlie's hand.
Charlie!
Hold your brother's
hand, okay?
- Don't let him go.
- ELLA: It's okay.
I love you.
WOMAN: Is everything all right?
- Dad?
- DAD: I love you.
- ELLA: Dad.
- It's fine.
- Dad.
- I'm just going to my car.
- Dad, where are you going?
- I'll be right back.
- No, no, sir.
WOMAN: Sir,
you can't leave now.
Sir, you cannot leave
your children here!
Dad! Daddy!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Daddy! No! No, Daddy!
- [sobbing]
- ELLA: No! Dad! No!
Dad, I'm sorry!
Dad! Dad! No!
- Are you okay?
- Sweetheart.
Dad, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Dad!
I'm sorry!
No!
No! No!
[breathing heavily]
[sobbing]
[siren wailing]
I don't know what else to do.
Dad!
It's okay, Charlie.
[barking]
[train rattling]
[plane whooshing]
Hey, man,
no sleeping in my store.
I'm not gonna sleep.
I ain't no motel, so don't
be puttin' your head down
on my table.
I paid a dollar
for this coffee.
That means I have a right
to sit here and drink it.
I'm paying for it,
goddamn right!
I just want to sit here,
have a coffee,
rest my head for a little bit.
Is that too much to ask?
I couldn't do that!
- [indistinct shouting]
- Get out, now!
[ethereal music plays]
[birds chirping]
[alarm beeping]
[brakes whining]
[indistinct chatter]
- [Dad groans]
- You can't park here.
You can't park on this side
of the street today.
Street sweeping.
And normally I'm just supposed
to write you a ticket,
but I saw you in there.
I gotta swing back
in 20 minutes.
If you're still here,
I gotta ticket the car.
Okay, thank you
for letting me know.
Good day, sir.
[direction indicator beeping]
- ELLA: Ready?
- [car door creaks open]
DAD: Ella, get in.
Get in!
[engine stalling]
[engine whirring]
[engine stalls]
[engine stalling]
[siren wailing]
[PA system chiming]
[indistinct chatter]
Good one.
[siren wailing]
They're not here.
Can you come inside with me?
[car honks]
You know, I think it's best
if you come inside with me.
[baby crying]
[phone ringing]
What's your name?
Martin Harper.
Well, hi, Martin.
I'm Edie.
Your children's names
are Charlie and Ella?
I have some paperwork for you.
MARTIN: Mmm.
EDIE: And their mother?
She passed.
I'm sorry to hear that.
They were pretty shaken
last night.
But eventually
they ate something
and they got some sleep.
And they...
they seem like
really good kids.
Hmm.
[Martin sobs]
When you left them...
it started a protocol.
A social worker has been
assigned to their case.
Do you understand that...
you're not going to see
your kids for a while?
That social services
picked them up?
Martin.
I mean, it's what
they deserve, right?
A stable home?
I think I need some help.
[Charlie laughs]
I got one.
- Thanks.
- It's heavy, right?
- Look at this, dad.
- Wow.
Can you even carry it?
Let me try.
ELLA: Yeah,
try throwing it again.
[all groan]
[Martin exclaims]
[Charlie screams]
MARTIN: On your mark.
Get set.
Go!
["Deep Water"
by Ed Askew plays]
[woman clears throat]
♪ Water is deep ♪
♪ The road goes on forever ♪
♪ And someday we'll make ♪
♪ This world
a little brighter ♪
♪ The rain is sweet ♪
♪ The cows are
in the clover ♪
♪ And when we meet ♪
♪ Someday we'll be closer ♪
♪ The sky is wide ♪
♪ The rivers flow together ♪
♪ And when they meet ♪
♪ The waves go out forever ♪
♪ Water is deep ♪
♪ The road goes on forever ♪
♪ And someday we'll make ♪
♪ This world
a little brighter ♪
[somber music plays]